{
	"questions": [
	    {
			"question": "How many NBA titles Michael Jordan won",
			"answer": ["2","4","7","6"],
			"correct": "6"
		},
		{
			"question": "Diego Maradona ended his career in what club",
			"answer": ["Napoli","Barcelona","Juventus","Boca Juniors"],
			"correct": "Boca Juniors"
		},
		{
			"question": "Roger Federer won how many Grand Slam's in his career by the end of 2019 season",
			"answer": ["12","9","16","20"],
			"correct": "20"
		},
		{
			"question": "How many World Cup titles Germany won",
			"answer": ["2","5","1","4"],
			"correct": "4"
		},
		{
			"question": "Who won Champions League 2018",
			"answer": ["Bayern Munich","Manchester United","Liverpool","Real Madrid"],
			"correct": "Real Madrid"
		},{
			"question": "Who won UEFA Men's Player of the Year award for 2017/18",
			"answer": ["Cristiano Ronaldo","Kylian Mbappé","Lionel Messi","Luka Modrić"],
			"correct": "Luka Modrić"
		},
		{
			"question": "Who holds the 100m world record",
			"answer": ["Carl Lewis","Ben Johnson","Linford Christie","Usain Bolt"],
			"correct": "Usain Bolt"
		},
		{
			"question": "Who was the champion of the Tour de France from 1999 to 2005",
			"answer": ["Chris Froome","Cadel Evans","Bernard Hinault","Lance Armstrong"],
			"correct": "Lance Armstrong"
		},
		{
			"question": "Mike Tyson lost his titles in a fight against",
			"answer": ["Evander Holyfield","Lennox Lewis","Michael Spinks","Buster Douglas"],
			"correct": "Buster Douglas"
		},
		{
			"question": "What was the last team Michael Jordan played for",
			"answer": ["LA Lakers","Chicago Bulls","Detroit Pistons","Washington Wizards"],
			"correct": "Washington Wizards"
		},
		{
			"question": "Who holds the world record in pole vault",
			"answer": ["Sergey Bubka","Maksim Tarasov","Sam Kendricks","Renaud Lavillenie"],
			"correct": "Renaud Lavillenie"
		},
		{
			"question": "How many times has Michael Schumacher been a Formula 1 champion",
			"answer": ["9","5","3","7"],
			"correct": "7"
		},
		{
			"question": "How many fights did Muhammad Ali lose during his professional career",
			"answer": ["1","3","none","5"],
			"correct": "5"
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the national sport in Japan",
			"answer": ["Karate","Boxing","Aikido","Sumo Wrestling"],
			"correct": "Sumo Wrestling"
		},
		{
			"question": "In which country were the first Olympic Games held",
			"answer": ["Italy","France","Spain","Greece"],
			"correct": "Greece"
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the largest stadium in the world",
			"answer": ["Camp Nou","Azteca Stadium in Mexico city","Melbourne Cricket Ground","Rungrado 1st of May Stadium"],
			"correct": "Rungrado 1st of May Stadium"
		}
		
	]
}
